dominos.ca 2014-03-27

# Domino's Pizza Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information has always been fundamental to the way we do business at Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. whether on the telephone, at our Stores or on our Web site or Applications. We believe in protecting the privacy of the personal information that we obtain for business purposes about our customers, employees, franchisees, suppliers and other entities. We strive to provide you with the best customer service in our mission to be the best pizza delivery company in the world. To us, that includes treating you fairly and with respect. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. will take reasonable steps to protect your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable law. This privacy policy does not apply to personal information of employees and franchisees of Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. 

### WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION

"Personal Information" means information about an identifiable individual, but does not include the name, title or business address or telephone number of an employee of an organization. 

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. sells product through delivery and take-out services and in order to provide you with our product and with these services we collect your name, email address and telephone. Payment information may be collected for the sole purpose of processing your order and receiving payment of the same. 

### HOW DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. collects personal information which you provide to it voluntarily, for example: request for home delivery of product, respond to offers, queries or complaints, participate in one of our contests, sweepstakes or surveys. 

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. may obtain your personal information from third parties, such as our affiliates, our franchisees, or our marketing partners in order to serve you better, to improve our products and services, to develop and advance the business system of Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. and to ensure complete customer satisfaction. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. complies with this privacy policy and all applicable privacy laws in the collection, use, disclosure and protection of all personal information that it receives. Any entity with which or from whom we share personal information is required to comply with all applicable privacy laws. 

### HOW DO WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION

Internal Business Purposes 

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. uses the personal information you provide for the purposes for which it was provided, for example to process a request for home delivery of product; to respond to queries or complaints; to notify you that you have won a prize, contest or sweepstakes. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. uses your Personal Information to better understand your needs, to improve our products and services, to develop and advance the business system of Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. and to ensure better customer satisfaction. 

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd.'s Direct Marketing Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. may use your personal information for contacting you about products and services, special offers and upcoming promotions or events offered by us, our affiliates, or our marketing partners that we think may be of interest to you for the purposes of marketing. If you prefer that we not use your personal information for direct marketing, you may opt-out of such uses by sending an email to: the Privacy Manager, [privacymanager@dominos.ca](mailto:privacymanager@dominos.ca) or write to: Privacy Manager, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. P.O. Box 21010, 500 Manning Road, Windsor, Ontario N8N 4S1 or call (519) 326-5280 (Monday to Friday 8 am - 5 pm MST). Any subsequent registration or request, either oral or in writing, for our services or participation in our sweepstakes, contest or surveys may void, temporarily or permanently, your prior elections to opt out of receiving marketing materials from Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd.. Once you have opted out from our direct marketing, please review all applicable rules and regulations before participating in any contests, sweepstakes, surveys, promotions or services. 

### WHEN AND HOW DO WE DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. utilizes third party suppliers, vendors and service providers to undertake various tasks on our behalf, such as delivery of our product, analyzing and sorting data, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and hosting and maintaining databases. These organizations may have access to personal information to the extent needed to perform their functions, but they may not use it for other purposes, such as marketing their products and services to you or providing your information to third parties. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. may, for the purposes of its business transactions, share personal information with its professional advisors, suppliers, franchisees, or agencies. Any entity with which we share personal information is required to comply with all applicable privacy laws. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. does not sell your personal information. 

Where permitted or required by law, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your consent, for example to comply with a subpoena or warrant issued or an order made by a court, to collect a debt you owe to us. 

### HOW DO YOU CONSENT

By providing us with your personal information, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of that information as described in this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time or as described at or before the time of collection, use or disclosure, as the case may be. If you do not want your personal information to be collected, used or disclosed in this manner, please do not submit your personal information to us or exercise opt-out procedures described above or as may be offered at the time of collection. If you have submitted personal information to us and wish to withdraw your consent to its retention, use or disclosure, please send an email to: Privacy Manager at [privacymanager@dominos.ca](mailto:privacymanager@dominos.ca) or write to: Privacy Manager, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. P.O. Box 21010, 500 Manning Road, Windsor, Ontario N8N 4S1 or call (519) 326-5280. You may withdraw your consent, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. 

### HOW DO WE PROTECT

We will protect your information with appropriate safeguards and security measures. We have implemented physical, technological and organizational procedures designed to protect the integrity and security of your personal information based on the nature, sensitivity and format of the personal information collected, used, stored or disclosed by Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. We will retain your personal information only for the time it is required and for the purposes for which it was collected. Only employees and agents of Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. who need to access your personal information in the course of their duties will have access to it. 

### HOW CAN YOU CORRECT OR ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We will make every reasonable effort to keep personal information as complete, accurate and current as is necessary to fulfill the purpose(s) for which it was collected. It is your right to have access to the personal information which you provided to us. Any request to this end should be sent to our Privacy Manager in writing at the following address: 

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd   
Attn: Privacy Manager   
P.O. Box 21010   
500 Manning Road   
Windsor, Ontario   
N8N 4S1 

We will respond to your request within a reasonable time, at minimal or no cost. Please note that we may not be able to provide personal information found on you which contains references to third parties as well as information that is subject to legal privilege, contains confidential information proprietary to Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd., related to an investigation of a breach of an agreement or a contravention of the law, or cannot be disclosed for other legal reasons. 

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time to address the changing needs of our business and / or to ensure compliance with applicable privacy laws. 

If you have any inquiries, complaints, questions or requests regarding this Privacy Policy, please send an email to: Privacy Manager at [privacymanager@dominos.ca](mailto:privacymanager@dominos.ca) or write to: Privacy Manager, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. P.O. Box 21010, 500 Manning Road, Windsor, Ontario N8N 4S1 or call (519) 326-5280. 

### OUR ONLINE PRIVACY POLICY

Protecting your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information has always been fundamental to the way we do business at Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. whether on the telephone, at our Stores or on our Web site or Applications. 

We strive to provide you with the best customer service in our mission to be the best pizza delivery company in the world. To us, that includes treating you fairly and with respect. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. will take reasonable steps to protect your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and applicable law. 

Your use of this Web site or Application constitutes your acceptance of this Privacy Policy and your consent to the practices it describes. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. web site or applications will not collect any personal information on this Web site or Applications unless you voluntarily provide it to us. For example, if you participate in one of our contests, sweepstakes or surveys, email us or send us other communication or to opt-in to receive Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. information through this Web site or Applications. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. uses the personal information you provide for the purposes for which it was provided. 

If you do not want us to obtain your personal information, please do not supply it to us. Even though you may choose not to provide/ submit personal information and you still will be able to visit most of the Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. Web site or Applications but you may not be able to enjoy certain personalized features. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. is the sole owner. 

### FRANCHISEE PERSONAL INFORMATION

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. Web site or Applications also acts as a communication portal with our franchisees. Only franchisees and employees of Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. can become registered users of Franchisee Login on Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. Web site or Applications. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. may collect personal information of its franchisees for this purpose including, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, a unique individual username and a unique individual password. 

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. Franchisees seeking more information or details regarding the above may contact their Franchise Business Consultant or write to: The Marketing Team, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd., P.O. Box 21010, 500 Manning Road, Windsor, Ontario N8N 4S1 or call toll free at: (519) 326-5280. 

### INFORMATION COLLECTED USING TECHNOLOGY

We may collect some information about you using technology, so it may not be readily apparent to you that it is being collected. For instance, when you come to our site your IP address is collected so that we know where to send information you are requesting. 

### COOKIE TECHNOLOGY

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. website's server, or the servers of companies that are used to operate this site or application, may place a "cookie" on your computer in order to allow you to use the website or applications and to personalize your experience. A "cookie" is a small piece of data that can be sent by a web server to your computer, which then may be stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow us to recognize your computer while you are on our website or applications and help customize your online experience and make it more convenient for you. Cookies are also useful in allowing more efficient log-in for users, tracking transaction histories and preserving information between sessions. The information collected from cookies may also be used to improve the functionality of the website or applications. Most web browser applications (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator) have features that can notify you when you receive a cookie or prevent cookies from being sent. If you disable cookies, however, you may not be able to use certain personalized functions of this website or application. 

### EXTERNAL LINKS

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. web site or applications may contain links to other Web sites or Applications not maintained or related to Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. These links are provided as a service to users and are not sponsored by or affiliated with this web site or application, or Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. has not reviewed any or all of the sites or applications hyper-linked to or from this web site or application and is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other Web sites or Applications. The links are accessed at the user's own risk, and Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. makes no representations or warranties about the content, completeness or accuracy of these links or the sites or applications hyper-linked to this Web site or Applications. Web sites or Applications that are accessible by hyperlinks from the Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. Web site or Applications may use cookies. Domino's Pizza encourages you to read the privacy statements provided by other Web sites or Applications before you provide personal information to them. Domino's Pizza of Canada ltd. does not implicitly endorse third-party sites or applications hyper-linked to this Web site or Application. 

### SECURITY

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to help guard personal information. If transactions are offered on the web site or applications, transaction information is transmitted to and from Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. restricts authorized access to your personal information to those persons who have a legitimate purpose to know that information to provide products or services to you and those persons you have authorized to have access to such information. Please be aware, however, that any email or other transmission you send through the internet cannot be completely protected against unauthorized interception. 

### CHILDREN'S POLICY

This Web site or Application is directed toward and designed for use by persons aged 13 or older. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. will not approve applications of, or establish or maintain registrations for any child whom Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. knows to be under the age of 13. Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. does not solicit or knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. nevertheless discovers that it has received personal information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. otherwise has reason to believe is, under the age of 13, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. will delete such information from its systems. Additionally, a child's parent or legal guardian may request that the child's information be corrected or deleted by requesting the same via an email to Privacy Manager at [privacymanager@dominos.ca](mailto:privacymanager@dominos.ca) or write to: Privacy Manager, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. P.O. Box 21010, 500 Manning Road, Windsor, Ontario N8N 4S1 or call (519) 326-5280. 

### LEGAL DISCLAIMER

Although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information as follows: i. when required by law to comply with a judicial proceeding, a court order, or legal process served on us; ii. to protect users of our Web site or Applications and our Web site or Applications from fraudulent or abusive use. 

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. reserves the right to modify or supplement this policy at any time. If a material change to the terms of this policy is made, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. will post a notice on its homepage and a link to the new policy. If you wish to change or delete your registration information or opt-out of any promotional materials please contact us via an email to Privacy Manager at [privacymanager@dominos.ca](mailto:privacymanager@dominos.ca) or write to: Privacy Manager, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. P.O. Box 21010, 500 Manning Road, Windsor, Ontario N8N 4S1 or call (519) 326-5280. 

If for any reason you feel that we have not followed our stated policy please let us know by e-mail at [privacymanager@dominos.ca](mailto:privacymanager@dominos.ca) or write to: Privacy Manager, Domino's Pizza of Canada Ltd. P.O. Box 21010, 500 Manning Road, Windsor, Ontario N8N 4S1 or call (519) 326-5280. We will look into your concern and try to resolve any problem.
